Guide to the Estela and Ernesto Bravo Film and Video Collection TAM.616
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series XXXIII: Unprocessed, 590972
  - Resquet Disscuiso y buenas Cavras, cuid18717; 467529 (Box 20, Cassette 524)
  - Hogar de R. Rosa, cuid18718; 467528 (Box 20, Cassette 525)
  - Little Havana Rec. Center, cuid18719; 467527 (Box 20, Cassette 526)
  - Granados, cuid18720; 467526 (Box 20, Cassette 527)
  - Mike Psyct, cuid18721; 467525 (Box 20, Cassette 528)
  - Entrevistas- Expocuba, cuid18722; 467524 (Box 20, Cassette 529)
  - Ana Rosa y Damian, cuid18723; 467523 (Box 23, Cassette 530)
  - Salvation Army, cuid18724; 467985 (Box 3, Cassette 68)
  - Aeropuerto Religioso, cuid18725; 467522 (Box 23, Cassette 531)
  - Interview with man from commando and woman from FAC, cuid18726; 467521 (Box 23, Cassette 532)
  - Fuste, cuid18727; 467520 (Box 23, Cassette 533)
  - Nyere OSPAAC, cuid18728; 467519 (Box 23, Cassette 534)
  - Ninas- Ninos Peguenos, cuid18729; 467518 (Box 23, Cassette 535)
  - imagenes de personas que esperon, cuid18730; 467517 (Box 23, Cassette 536)
  - Iglesia Ninos- Toma, cuid18731; 467515 (Box 23, Cassette 538)
  - Entrevista Joven que Regreso de EV en barco, cuid18732; 467514 (Box 23, Cassette 539)
  - Entrevista con Eric, cuid18733; 467512 (Box 23, Cassette 541)
  - Miami-Habana, cuid18734; 467511 (Box 23, Cassette 542)
  - Lourdes, cuid18735; 467510 (Box 23, Cassette 543)
  - Anglada- Granados, cuid18736; 467509 (Box 23, Cassette 544)
  - Habana-5, cuid18737; 467508 (Box 23, Cassette 545)
  - Escuela (Fac. De Medicina), cuid18738; 467507 (Box 23, Cassette 546)
  - Caf Roma Negro Poeta, cuid18739; 467506 (Box 23, Cassette 547)
  - Cubanos que Fueror invitados a los Fuegos, cuid18740; 467505 (Box 23, Cassette 548)
  - Katutura- Namibios Berados en Cuba, cuid18741; 467504 (Box 23, Cassette 549)
  - Estela Bravo, cuid18742; 467502 (Box 23, Cassette 551)
  - Hospital Hogar Custo Herido, cuid18743; 467501 (Box 23, Cassette 552)
  - Estacion de Telefonos Publicos Lisa, cuid18744; 467500 (Box 23, Cassette 553)
  - Despues de Pobladoes Calle Baricada, cuid18745; 467499 (Box 23, Cassette 554)
  - Salida Rafts cojimar- Leaving Cuba, cuid18746; 467498 (Box 27, Cassette 555)
  - Street Interviews Havana, cuid18747; 467497 (Box 27, Cassette 556)
  - Bump 2- Key West, cuid18748; 467496 (Box 27, Cassette 557)
  - Silvio good-nicaragua, cuid18749; 467495 (Box 27, Cassette 558)
  - Sylvio y Pablo, cuid18751; 467494 (Box 27, Cassette 559)
  - Coast Guard Lt. Howe, cuid18752; 467493 (Box 24, Cassette 560)
  - Fruit Stand Homeless Woman, cuid18750; 467492 (Box 24, Cassette 561)
  - Hogar de Ana Rosa, cuid18753; 467491 (Box 24, Cassette 562)
  - Images para documental omnibustransito, cuid18754; 467490 (Box 24, Cassette 563)
  - Balseros Wayne Smith, cuid18755; 467489 (Box 24, Cassette 564)
  - Salvation Army/Coast Guard, cuid18756; 467486 (Box 24, Cassette 567)
  - Manifestacions Bicentario- Mujeres- Bailes, cuid18757; 467484 (Box 24, Cassette 569)
  - Cuanto Tiempo Hace Guanaracoa, cuid18758; 467482 (Box 24, Cassette 571)
  - Aruca en estudio de Radio Progresso, cuid18759; 467481 (Box 24, Cassette 572)
  - Hogar de Ana Rosa..., cuid18760; 467480 (Box 25, Cassette 573)
  - Balseros Church World Service, cuid18761; 467479 (Box 25, Cassette 574)
  - Eric Playing Piano, cuid18762; 467478 (Box 25, Cassette 575)
  - Parque Central 98, cuid18763; 467477 (Box 25, Cassette 576)
  - Last of Conrado Museo de Balseros, cuid18764; 467476 (Box 25, Cassette 577)
  - Ana Rosa y Damian, cuid18765; 467475 (Box 25, Cassette 578)
  - 11 Granados, cuid18766; 467474 (Box 25, Cassette 579)
  - 13 Granados, cuid18767; 467473 (Box 25, Cassette 580)
  - Anglada 10, cuid18768; 467472 (Box 25, Cassette 581)
  - 43R, cuid18769; 467471 (Box 25, Cassette 582)
  - Street interviews, cuid18770; 467470 (Box 25, Cassette 583)
  - Negocios Cubanos en Miami, cuid18771; 467469 (Box 25, Cassette 584)
  - Union City, cuid18772; 467468 (Box 25, Cassette 585)
  - Rostros Solendo, cuid18773; 467467 (Box 25, Cassette 586)
  - Habana Bandera Compo, cuid18774; 467466 (Box 25, Cassette 587)
  - Cuba travel, cuid18775; 467464 (Box 25, Cassette 589)
  - Argentina, cuid18776; 467461 (Box 26, Cassette 592)
  - Argentina, cuid18777; 467460 (Box 26, Cassette 593)
  - Argentina, cuid18778; 467454 (Box 26, Cassette 599)
  - Mama del Nino, cuid18779; 467453 (Box 26, Cassette 600)
  - Argentina, cuid18780; 467452 (Box 26, Cassette 601)
  - Peru Titon, cuid18781; 467450 (Box 26, Cassette 603)
  - Peru Footage of Peru Hospital, cuid18782; 467449 (Box 26, Cassette 604)
  - Argentina, cuid18783; 467448 (Box 26, Cassette 605)
  - Peru, cuid18784; 467447 (Box 26, Cassette 606)
  - Col Peru Special Col Hector Mondregon, cuid18785; 467446 (Box 26, Cassette 607)
  - Cape Town Angola SAA, cuid18786; 467445 (Box 28, Cassette 608)
  - Converciones paz Cuba, cuid18787; 467444 (Box 28, Cassette 609)
  - Namibia, cuid18788; 467443 (Box 28, Cassette 610)
  - Locutor ECITVAR, cuid18789; 467442 (Box 28, Cassette 611)
  - Afravision Compilation Cape Town Webster Funeral, cuid18790; 467441 (Box 28, Cassette 612)
  - South Africa- Dick Wilson- D. Soweto, cuid18791; 467440 (Box 28, Cassette 613)
  - Castanel, cuid18792; 467439 (Box 28, Cassette 614)
  - ICRT (Irma Caceres) en avion..., cuid18793; 467438 (Box 28, Cassette 615)
  - Caras Guerra, cuid18794; 467437 (Box 28, Cassette 616)
  - ICRT New York, cuid18795; 467436 (Box 28, Cassette 617)
  - CAS 1 Angola, cuid18796; 467435 (Box 28, Cassette 618)
  - Defile Botha Fidel..., cuid18797; 467434 (Box 28, Cassette 619)
  - Bump 8, cuid18798; 467433 (Box 28, Cassette 620)
  - 3er Corte, cuid18799; 467432 (Box 28, Cassette 621)
  - Prisoners Tutu, cuid18800; 467431 (Box 28, Cassette 622)
  - ECITVFAR Namibia, cuid18801; 467429 (Box 28, Cassette 624)
  - ECITVFAR A-1624, cuid18802; 467428 (Box 28, Cassette 625)
  - Quien Gano, cuid18803; 467427 (Box 32, Cassette 626)
  - Carlos Muniz, cuid18804; 467419 (Box 33, Cassette 634)
  - Formato C, cuid18805; 467418 (Box 33, Cassette 635)
  - Bump 1, cuid18806; 467417 (Box 33, Cassette 636)
  - Edicion en bloque cassette n 22, cuid18807; 467416 (Box 33, Cassette 637)
  - Chile, cuid18808; 467413 (Box 27, Cassette 640)
  - Chile, cuid18809; 467412 (Box 27, Cassette 641)
  - Chile, cuid18810; 467411 (Box 27, Cassette 642)
  - Madame Godoy, cuid18811; 467409 (Box 27, Cassette 644)
  - Chile, cuid18812; 467406 (Box 27, Cassette 647)
  - Chile, cuid18813; 467405 (Box 27, Cassette 648)
  - 3 Ninos, cuid18814; 467403 (Box 27, Cassette 650)
  - CH 27, cuid18815; 467402 (Box 27, Cassette 651)
  - Cemeteno Godoy, cuid18816; 467401 (Box 27, Cassette 652)
  - Ninos Chiquitos, cuid18817; 467400 (Box 27, Cassette 653)
  - Juicu Sonielo, cuid18818; 467396 (Box 29, Cassette 657)
  - Jotar Casa, cuid18819; 467395 (Box 29, Cassette 658)
  - Fotos, cuid18820; 467394 (Box 29, Cassette 659)
  - Gatica, cuid18821; 467384 (Box 30, Cassette 669)
  - Estela en Escuela Tatiana, cuid18822; 467383 (Box 30, Cassette 670)
  - Campo Mayo, cuid18823; 467381 (Box 30, Cassette 672)
  - Mandela in Cuba II, cuid18824; 467377 (Box 31, Cassette 676)
  - Venceremos Brigade, cuid18825; 467375 (Box 31, Cassette 678)
  - Prisioners, cuid18826; 467364 (Box 34, Cassette 689)
  - BUMP, cuid18827; 467363 (Box 34, Cassette 690)
  - Headquarters of CNM, cuid18828; 467362 (Box 34, Cassette 691)
  - Union City, cuid18829; 467358 (Box 34, Cassette 695)
  - Street Scenes Havana- Hotels- Tourist Shop; Families say Goodbye, cuid18830; 467357 (Box 34, Cassette 696)
  - Nicaragua-2 Reportajes, cuid18831; 467356 (Box 34, Cassette 697)
  - Union City, cuid18832; 467355 (Box 34, Cassette 698)
  - Medicos en Nicaragua, cuid18833; 467354 (Box 34, Cassette 699)
  - Campo y Mantanas Cubanas- Cubanos de Miami, cuid18834; 467353 (Box 34, Cassette 700)
  - Union City, cuid18835; 467351 (Box 34, Cassette 702)
  - Rosenburg Kids 1, cuid18836; 467349 (Box 36, Cassette 704)
  - Entrevista Nicolas Rosenberg, cuid18837; 467348 (Box 36, Cassette 705)
  - Rosenburg Kids 1, cuid18838; 467347 (Box 36, Cassette 706)
  - Hijos Rosenberg, cuid18839; 467346 (Box 36, Cassette 707)
  - Rosenburg Kids 2, cuid18840; 467345 (Box 36, Cassette 708)
  - Rosenburg Kids 3, cuid18841; 467344 (Box 36, Cassette 709)
  - Dalo en Cuba, cuid18842; 467341 (Box 36, Cassette 712)
  - Isla Juventud, cuid18843; 467339 (Box 36, Cassette 714)
  - Guaguanco, cuid18844; 467337 (Box 36, Cassette 716)
  - Cancel Miranda, cuid18845; 467336 (Box 36, Cassette 717)
  - Rosenburgs, cuid18846; 467335 (Box 36, Cassette 718)
  - Havana University, cuid18847; 467331 (Box 38, Cassette 722)
  - Times Sq. Visual, cuid18848; 467329 (Box 38, Cassette 724)
  - Heidi Angloda, cuid18849; 467326 (Box 40, Cassette 727)
  - Aruca in Studio, cuid18850; 467325 (Box 40, Cassette 728)
  - Aruca - Suffering Cuban Families, cuid18851; 467324 (Box 40, Cassette 729)
  - Entrevistas Escorias Cassette Linico, cuid18852; 467322 (Box 40, Cassette 731)
  - Filmacion de la contra fronta a la Mision- Harold (CNN), cuid18853; 467321 (Box 40, Cassette 732)
  - KKK, cuid18854; 467316 (Box 40, Cassette 737)
  - Maxito Pacieute Patricia, cuid18855; 467313 (Box 40, Cassette 740)
  - Pitch 3, cuid18856; 467310 (Box 40, Cassette 743)
  - Alicia Alonso DAEFA, cuid18857; 467308 (Box 42, Cassette 745)
  - Mercedes y Matilda- "Contingente Blas Roca" Alexander Espino, cuid18858; 467307 (Box 42, Cassette 746)
  - Baudilio Castellanos, cuid18859; 467306 (Box 42, Cassette 747)
  - Ket-18, cuid18860; 467303 (Box 42, Cassette 750)
  - C.15362, cuid18861; 467301 (Box 42, Cassette 752)
  - Ecitvfar, cuid18862; 467295 (Box 42, Cassette 758)
  - Alicia Alonso Lima, cuid18863; 467293 (Box 42, Cassette 760)
  - Circulo "Lornas del Bosque Jardin- Entrevista a Mercedes y Matilda Espino, cuid18864; 467292 (Box 42, Cassette 761)
  - At Airport Jose Marti Interviews with people waiting for relatives, cuid18865; 467291 (Box 42, Cassette 762)
  - 2 Formato C, cuid18866; 467290 (Box 33, Cassette 800)
  - Edicion en bloque cassette n 4, cuid18867; 467289 (Box 33, Cassette 801)
  - Bump 4, cuid18868; 467288 (Box 33, Cassette 802)
  - Chandra Fidel, cuid18869; 467286 (Box 35, Cassette 804)
  - Brasil Jacunto Diaz, cuid18870; 467285 (Box 35, Cassette 805)
  - Prestes 7A, cuid18871; 467283 (Box 35, Cassette 807)
  - Rio Vidigal Gravado, cuid18872; 467282 (Box 35, Cassette 808)
  - Campesinos Only, cuid18873; 467279 (Box 35, Cassette 811)
  - Alicia Alonso T. Colon, cuid18874; 467278 (Box 35, Cassette 812)
  - Aragon Concert Rough Edit, cuid18875; 467277 (Box 35, Cassette 813)
  - Brasil Chico Casa, cuid18876; 467275 (Box 35, Cassette 815)
  - Brasil Chico B, cuid18877; 467274 (Box 35, Cassette 816)
  - Brasil Chico B Chico B, cuid18878; 467273 (Box 35, Cassette 817)
  - Jose Marti S. Paulo, cuid18879; 467272 (Box 35, Cassette 818)
  - Salvation Army Ermita de la caridada, cuid18880; 467271 (Box 35, Cassette 819)
  - Cubatravel 3, cuid18881; 467270 (Box 37, Cassette 820)
  - Marcos Afri Campanientp, cuid18882; 467269 (Box 37, Cassette 821)
  - Satellite Academy Stories, cuid18883; 467268 (Box 37, Cassette 822)
  - Luciano Nieves, cuid18884; 467267 (Box 37, Cassette 823)
  - Espinosa Rodrigues, cuid18885; 467266 (Box 37, Cassette 824)
  - Maceitos 3 42R, cuid18886; 467265 (Box 37, Cassette 825)
  - Reportate Bergandaline 4 Padre Yolanda, cuid18887; 467263 (Box 37, Cassette 827)
  - Rosario Morello Embanada del Peru en Cuba, cuid18888; 467262 (Box 37, Cassette 828)
  - American Club 2, cuid18889; 467261 (Box 37, Cassette 829)
  - Jenny and Gloria (NOTE: Even though the Packing Slip indicates Miami-Havana, the filming dates are associated with the Excludables.), Nov 22, 1992; cuid18890; 479519 (Box 51, Cassette ref1177)
  - Dopice final dialog, cuid18891; 467260 (Box 37, Cassette 830)
  - Julia Alemany habla de "Abdala", cuid18892; 467258 (Box 37, Cassette 832)
  - Nieves Widow Sauve Factory, cuid18893; 467257 (Box 37, Cassette 833)
  - Nieto Raul Matinez Marco Martin, cuid18894; 467256 (Box 37, Cassette 834)
  - Martinez final dialogo rollo 2, cuid18895; 467254 (Box 37, Cassette 836)
  - Walsh Cutaways Church NJ, cuid18896; 467253 (Box 37, Cassette 837)
  - Ciudad Libertad Dina, cuid18897; 467249 (Box 39, Cassette 841)
  - Deparo de lu digital, cuid18898; 467247 (Box 39, Cassette 843)
  - "hogar de cristo y poblaciones", cuid18903; 467240 (Box 39, Cassette 850)
  - Maribel Acosto Cogimar, cuid18899; 467239 (Box 39, Cassette 851)
  - Estadio, cuid18900; 467238 (Box 39, Cassette 852)
  - Ciudada Libertad, cuid18901; 467236 (Box 39, Cassette 854)
  - ECITUFAR, cuid18902; 467235 (Box 41, Cassette 855)
  - Plaza Revacto 1o Mayo, cuid18904; 467231 (Box 41, Cassette 859)
  - Musica Bajada Barco, cuid18905; 467226 (Box 41, Cassette 864)
  - TV de Espana "De Pelicula" interview E Bravo, cuid18906; 467215 (Box 43, Cassette 875)
  - Dr Tom's Township SWAPO, cuid18907; 467213 (Box 43, Cassette 877)
  - [Mina, Gianni] (Not legible label but "Fidel Tapes" identifies as Mina), cuid18908; 479398 (Box 62, Cassette ref1059)
- Unprocessed posters from accession 2016.20, cuid18910 (Flat-file-folder 2)